https://herbalhealer.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

ALERT! Shipments may take longer in transit than normal, due to shipping company delays from Covid-19.
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our store! Your privacy is top priority to us. To better protect your privacy when using our site, we provide this notice to explain our online information practices and the choices you have about how your information is collected and used. Information We CollectYou provide personal information during registration and online purchases from our site. This information includes: your name, email, address, phone number, payment information, and order specific data. We also collect non-personal information including: specific pages visited, frequency of page visits, the type of device you are using, and which browser you are using.How We Use the InformationWe use the information provided to complete the ordering process, to update you on your order progress, and to respond to inquiries. We will also use this information to send you promotional mailings and sales. If you choose to opt out of the promotional mailings and sales information you can do so at checkout. If you choose to be removed from our mailing list and our system, please call our Customer Service Representatives. The non-personal information collected may be used to better design our site and to make it more user friendly. It is also used to analyze the site usage. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information for the following reasons: legal process (ex. court order, subpoena), law enforcement request, or a charge-back inquiry from our merchant bank. We will not sell, trade, or transfer your personal information to parties outside of our company except as described above.Collection of Information by Third Party SitesOur site may or may not include links to other sites. Visitors should review the other sites' privacy policy notices as we have no control over the information these third party sites collect or use.
Back to Top
Stay Up To Date
Sign up for specials and Herbal Healer news. We will communicate occasionally via email to provide you helpful information and savings.
Sign Up
*You can unsubscribe at anytime.
*You can unsubscribe at anytime.
